[Music]
Hello friends, I am Sarvesh and I
welcome you.
As you might have seen in the last video
that we are discussing more about the post office, the
post office has
recently launched an accidental insurance of Rs.
399. Its benefits are
visible on the left side. You are getting all these benefits in that
insurance.
This insurance is just accidental
insurance or something, if you
fall in your house then you get all that here.
It does not mean something like LIC type,
your life insurance etc.,
it is just an accidental insurance which is
also provided to you in the ATM cards of many banks. So this, I
mean, Pehle Chand, which is not at all of the post office,
Tata I's BHIM,
they have also started this in collaboration with the post office.
Okay, you will not get this insurance
in the post office, I mean, in all the post offices, so to get this,
you will have to go to the postman or
such post offices.  I will have to
go to the place where it
is not in the post and that is also the dealer office and that is the
most hit post office of the regional regent, you
can also get the map out, so should you get this
accidental insurance or
not, okay, so today we are going to discuss about this, so
let's
start the video, without any other scheme, do
watch the video till the end, ₹400 is a very small amount,
this is a premium for one year, you do not have to pay that much
every month, so if you cannot get ₹400 every
year, then still tell me, those who are
very good manual laborers can also get this, the
meaning of post office is the same,
everything is affordable for the common people, they get it out of the post office, okay, so
₹400 for you per year is
not that much, so according to me, you should definitely get this out,
if something happens in the future, do not adopt,
my subscribers and any
true accident of every citizen of this world is not
fatal, but still it goes home, so
after the song  If you have accidental accidents, then this
accidental insurance helps you a lot.
Look here, the one you can see
on the left side, it also says
that there is insurance up to 10 lakhs and your OPD
expenses are also included in it,
plus your two children will get one lakh rupees each
if you are fully injured
in an accident. According to me, this is the best
insurance you can get. You must go to the post office, that is, you
just have to take your Aadhar card with you. If you take
half of it, then this will be
your insurance as well. So
take much with you. There is no need for documents etc. in this, it is
okay,
just go early in the morning, then you will find the postman
quickly. There in the post office, this is the simple
process, so
definitely get the insurance done quickly.
They have launched the scheme just 3 months ago, so it hasn't been long.
Okay, guys,
if you liked this information, that's all there is
in today's video, then
like the channel and also
like the channel and the video.  You will also like it and
subscribe to the channel, okay
let's go nation